Anyone can commit murder.
High Heel Homicide is a thriller, horror film directed by Dean McKendrick.
As a string of brutal murders plague the city, two undercover
detectives race to solve the mystery and unmask the killer.
Their only clues: each victim is a former cop and each has
a blood-red letter painted on their body.
How many will have to die before the killer spells out their message in blood?
Rachel, played by Carter Cruise.
Sam, played by Brent Harvey.
Maggie, played by Mia Li.
Tom, played by Andrew Espinoza Long.
Ally, played by Blair Williams.
Sara, played by Pristine Edge.
Homicide is an Australian television police procedural drama series broadcast
on the Seven Network and produced by Crawford Productions.
It was the television successor to Crawfords' radio series D24.
After self-financing the pilot episode, Hector Crawford shopped it around commercial networks for nearly a year, before a series was commissioned in
1964 by Melbourne HSV7 station manager Keith Cairns, although HSV's partner station in Sydney, ATN, initially refused to participate.
The film explores themes of homicide, femme fatale,
series of murders, cowgirl, lesbian sex.
The tone is dark and intense.